mobafire.com 2019-12-31

# League of Legends Strategy Build Guide :: LoL Strategy Building Tool by MOBAFire

## Our Commitment to Privacy

MOBAFire Network is commited to protecting your privacy and complying with all global privacy laws to the best of our ability. To ensure we are as compliant as possible we collect very little information and we protect that information with strong security. To find out more about specific topics related to our privacy policies please read below.

## Our Policies

What information do we collect? 

MOBAFire collects very little personal information. You are free to use the site without giving us any personal information but if you register we need your email address, a user name and a password. If you log in with social media we associate and store your social media account with your MFN account. We collect information from you when you register on our site. We also record IP addresses for anonymous voting and other general security purposes.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## Google, and other third party vendors, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To provide advertisements targeted to your interests. Advertising supports our network and pays the bills to keep our services running at not cost to our users.

How do we protect your information? 

Our network of sites is hosted in the United States by top tier service providers who take privacy and security as seriously as you do. In order to protect the limited personal data we collect we implement physical, technial and administrative safeguards designed to keep data protected. Access to personal information is restricted to people who need it only.

Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

3rd Parties and Privacy 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

The following 3rd parties are considered trusted and are used throughout the MOBAFire Network:

  * [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy), [Google +](https://policies.google.com/privacy), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/en/privacy), [Battle.net](http://us.blizzard.com/en-us/company/about/privacy.html) and [Steam](https://store.steampowered.com/privacy_agreement/) are all used to for social logins and for sharing media. They all have their own privacy polocies that you would have agreed to in order to use thier services on our network. We do not have access to, or share any information with these services, we only receive a pass or fail response to your logins and we associate your social media account with your MFN account.
  * Google Analytics: Our network of sites use Google Analytics to process data about how our sites are used. We transmit usage data to Google in the United States for processing. Google stores this data for us to generate reports to help us understand how our sites are accessed and used. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. See [Google's privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You can opt out of Google Analytics by disabling or blocking the cookie, disabling JavaScript or use Google's [opt-out service](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)
  * Recaptcha is used to verify users are not bots when doing things like anonymous voting or submitting forms. See recaptcha (Google) [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) for more information.
  * Cloudflare is used to cache pages and speed up site delivery. To learn more about what data Cloudflare collects and how they use it view their [privacy policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/).
  * Venatus Media handles all advertising on our network. They collect data for direct and programmatic advertising sales through use of pixel trackers and ad tags. Learn more about [Venatus Media](https://www.venatusmedia.com/) and their [Privacy Policy](https://www.venatusmedia.com/privacy/).

Advertising 

Through Venatus Media we use a wide variety of other companies under agreements with us to serve third-party advertisements when you visit and use our network of sites. These companies may collect and use click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over during your visits to our network and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use tracking technologies to collect this information. Other companies' use of their tracking technologies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Compliance with regional privacy protection laws 

## GDPR

We strive to comply with the EU GDPR laws. We only collect personally identifiable information when registering on our site and this information only includes a user name, email and password. You may request the removal of this personal information at any time by emailing us at [support@mobafire.com](mailto:support@mobafire.com) regardelss of your location. Content created on our website is not considered personally identifiable and is not included as part of this agreement.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. We do not collect age, gender, location or other personal information about anyone.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy, the use of cookies and the use of our 3rd party partners. Information collected by registering on this site, specifically email, user name and password may be removed by emailing [support@mobafire.com](mailto:support@mobafire.com).

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any updates to our privacy policy will be posted on this page, and/or we'll update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 23, 2018
